[{"answer": "Why do you need to do this", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Who are you? Doctor... ", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "We", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Your... lover", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "my friend, I must apologize again, for the Kronos mishap.  It was a scary few minutes around here. Wow. But thank God, the complaint was found. And no damage was done", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "There won't be a next time, I guarantee it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " And I hate to rush you out of here, but..", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "... we've got a committee meeting", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " The guy sat in my office! You can't get AIDS that way, right", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "It doesn't travel through the air, by breathing, or touching, right", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " The partner who spotted the lesion, my friend, used to work for my friend, my friend, in D.C. There's a paralegal there, my friend. She's had lesions on and off for three years. She says it was common knowledge around the office that her lesions were caused by AIDS", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No. They didn't fire her", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I can heal myself", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I can heal myself", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I can heal myself", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I can heal myself", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Those are my cute little hand prints. And my brother's and my sister's", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Today is my parents' fortieth wedding anniversary", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "That's right", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Often, he does", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Apparently, Mr. my friend felt they were too...", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I said my earrings  American. They're Africa", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Aren't you", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Do I look gay to you? Relax", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I have too much work to do. Skip the treatment", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I said, skip it, my friend. It's my treatment", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What's wrong with you", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm not going to close th", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Close the law book", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "CLOSE THE FUCKING LAW BOOK", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It's not a costume, I just got off work. You're cute", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Absolutely. Want to see a picture of  baby", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Uh huh..", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend. Okay. my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What impressed you about him", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What kind of person is that", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I suppose you could say that", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I still am", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "In the years you worked at my friend, did you ever tell my friend you were gay", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Can you explain  you didn't", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "What makes you an excellent lawyer", "docId": "philadelphia.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What do you love about it", "qsentId": 42}]